My new book,
How Not to Age,
is out now!
If you’ve already preordered,
your book is on its way.
If you didn’t,
head to your local
public library
or favorite bookseller
to pick up a copy.
And if you’re gonna
get a stack
for everyone on your
holiday gift list,
please consider buying
them this week,
as first-week sales will
determine placement
on the New York Times
Best Seller list.
Fingers crossed How Not to Age
jumps to number one
so even more people will learn how
to take better care of themselves
and their loved ones.
I can’t wait for you to dive in and
hope you are as excited as I am
about the amazing science out there
on slowing the aging process
with evidence-based nutrition.